Guide to the Harry August Schoth Papers 1910-1970
Oregon State University Archives
- Field Notebooks, 1914-1960; Series VI
  - Vetch investigation (Homer M. Carnes), 1915-16 (Box 9)
  - Vetches, 1916 and 1917-18 (Box 9)
  - Vetches and horse beans, 1918-19 (Box 9)
  - Vetch notes - aphids, 1918 (Box 9)
  - Vetch plot plantings, succession trials, and Miscellaneous plantings, 1924-25 (Box 9)
  - Vetch & field pea plots, 1925-26 (Box 9)
  - Clover seedings, West Farm, 1922-1925 (Box 9)
  - Clover seedings, 1924-25 and 1925-26 (Box 9)
  - Red clover seedings, West Farm, 1926 (Box 9)
  - Special red clover seedings, sweet clover seedings, 1926 (Box 9)
  - Red clover volunteering trials-generation trials, beginning spring 1935 (East Farm, Granger) (Box 9)
  - Crimson & Miscellaneous clover nursery, 1938-39 (Box 9)
  - Threshing data (East Farm), 1932 (Box 9)
  - Threshing and cleaning (East Farm), 1939 (Box 9)
  - Alfalfa trials (East Farm), 1926 (Box 9)
  - Alfalfa (S.A. Stagner), 1930 (Box 9)
  - Alfalfa (S.A. Stagner) (Linn Co. Farm?), 1932 (Box 9)
  - Soybean trails, 1926 (Box 9)
  - Soybeans (books 1-3), 1927? (Box 9)
  - Soybeans 1927? (book 4), 1933 (5 books) and 1934? (Box 10)
  - Soy & mung beans (East Farm), 1934 (Box 10)
  - Soy & mung beans, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Soy & mung beans (also chick peas, perilla, sorghum, veg. beans, and squash) (East Farm), 1936 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous nursery seedings, Spring 1935 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous seedings (rapeseed, perilla, Miscellaneous legumes, crimson clover), spring & fall, 1936 (Box 10)
  - Artichokes (also soybeans and sorghum) (East Farm), 1932 (Box 10)
  - Artichokes (Jerusalem) (East Farm), 1932-33 (Box 10)
  - Artichokes, 1933-34 and 1935-36 (Box 10)
  - Rye grasses (East Farm), 1933 (Box 10)
  - Rye grass, 1958-59, Tall Fescue, 1959, & Harding grass, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Forage experimental work at Astoria, Oregon, 1921-22 (Box 10)
  - Horse beans, vetch, and sweet clover, undated (Box 10)
  - Division of Plant Exploration & Introduction - USDA seed germination tests, 1934 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Army notes (grass airfields in the Pacific Northwest), 1942-43; 3 books (Box 10)
  - Wiley Plunkett (Miscellaneous seedings), 1927, 1929 & 1930 (Box 10)
  - East & South Farms (various crops), 1930-31 (Box 10)
  - East Farm?, (various crops), 1931-32 (Box 10)
  - East Farm plots, 1933-34 (Box 10)
  - Field 12, Range 3, introductory nursery, 1958 (Box 10)
  - N.K. & Co. nursery (grasses), 1963 (Box 10)
  - Grass, vetch, alfalfa nurseries; clover, chick peas, soybeans, 1922 (Box 11)
  - Grass, pea and vetch nurseries (East Farm?), 1932-33 (Box 11)
  - Seeds to be sent out (East Farm), 1931? (Box 11)
  - Field notes, 1916-17 (Box 11)
  - Scale book for experimental work, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Various crops (West Farm), undated (Box 11)
  - Various plots, various farms (S.A. Stagner), 1926 (Box 11)
  - Averill Farm (S.A. Stagner), 1927 (Box 11)
  - Alfalfa? (Averill Farm), 1925 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 4 books (Box 11)
  - Time & Expense accounts (expenses of conducting forage work), July 1925-December 1932 (Box 11)
  - Farmer's Pocket Ledger (time & expense information), ca. 1934 (Box 11)
- Maps, Plans and Charts, 1905-1958; Series VII
  - Grazing Lands Western United States, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1905 (Map-case *)
  - Chart, Questions Regarding the Public Grazing Lands, 1905? (Map-case *)
  - State of Oregon Highway Dept. automobile road map, 1945 (Map-case *)
  - Sketch Plan Showing Planting and Fence Protection Against Sand Drift, Naval Radio Compass Station, Empire, Oregon, Jan. 17, 1927 (Map-case *)
  - Electrical Installation plan, Forage Crop Building, Oregon Agricultural College, March 25, 1931 (Map-case *)
  - Proposed Turf Plots, Oregon State College, June 30, 1952 (Map-case *)
  - Kentucky Bluegrass Pedigree Lines, Ferry-Morse Seed Co., ca. 1958 (Map-case *)
- Photographs, 1923-1959; Series VIII
  - USDA publication photographs of grasses and ground covers (taken in Corvallis), 1923 (Box 12)
  - Rows of legumes (horse beans, tangier peas, Swedish vetch), June 1927 (Box 12)
  - Grasses grown with different fertilizers, ca. 1930 (Box 12)
  - Samples of dried cover crop plants, ca. 1930 (Box 12)
  - Clear cut hillside, ca. 1930 (Box 12)
  - Annual Corvallis Seed School and Guzzle-fest, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Summer home, Wm. & Elizabeth Lane, Budd Lake, NJ, ca. 1955 (Box 12)
  - Jerusalem artichoke field, Budd Lake, NJ, ca. 1955 (Box 12)
  - Highway soil maintenance photographs (USDA), March 1957 (Box 12)
  - Grass grown from radiation-treated seed (USDA photo), 1959 (Box 12)
  - Cattle on winter bluegrass, undated (Box 12)
  - Unidentified group along roadside, undated (Box 12)
  - Distinguishing characters of seed of certain cultivated Lespedezas, undated (Box 12)
  - Glass negatives of 1923 USDA publication photographs (Box 13)